http://www.crossroadsbsa.org/resources/privacy-statement/

About
Who We AreDistrictsLeadershipMajor DonorsKeeping Scouts SafeEmployment Opportunities
Programs
What We DoCub ScoutingScouts BSAVenturingExploringSTEM ScoutsSea ScoutsAfter SchoolReaching for TomorrowAdditional Programs & TrainingsForms & Resources
Activities
Take AdvantageCommunityHigh AdventureJamboreeAlumniScout BandFirecrafterOrder of the ArrowScouting at Home
Join
Start Your AdventureWhy ScoutingLocate a UnitVolunteerFrequently Asked Questions
Support
Make a DonationMajor GiftsFundraising EventsFriends of ScoutingCommunity PartnershipsPopcorn
Contact
Find Staff MemberView Key VolunteersRequest InformationShare Your StorySubscribe to eNewsletter
Shop
Locate a ShopSpecialsResourcesOnline Store
Rent
View Rental OptionsFacilitiesEquipmentMake a Reservation
Español
Privacy Statement of Crossroads of America Council
Programs
Forms & Resources
Youth Protection Training
Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ)
Forms & Resources
Awards & Recognition
Camp 2020
Calendar
Commissioner
District Operations
Full Family Scouting
Ideal Year of Scouting
Youth Protection Training
Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ)
Forms & Resources
Awards & Recognition
Camp 2020
Calendar
Commissioner
District Operations
Full Family Scouting
Ideal Year of Scouting
Terms of Use
Crossroads of America Council is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Crossroads of America Council website and governs data collection and usage. By using the Crossroads of America Council website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.Collection of Personal InformationCrossroads of America Council collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Crossroads of America Council also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Crossroads of America Council. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Crossroads of America Council for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Crossroads of America Council Web site.Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Crossroads of America Council public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Crossroads of America Council does not read any of your private online communications.Crossroads of America Council encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Crossroads of America Council so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Crossroads of America Council is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Crossroads of America Council and Crossroads of America Council family of websites.Use of Personal InformationCrossroads of America Council collects and uses your personal information to operate the Crossroads of America Council website and deliver the services you have requested. Crossroads of America Council also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Crossroads of America Council and its affiliates. Crossroads of America Council may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.Crossroads of America Council does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Crossroads of America Council may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Crossroads of America Council may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Crossroads of America Council, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.Crossroads of America Council does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.Crossroads of America Council keeps track of the websites and pages our customers visit within Crossroads of America Council, in order to determine what Crossroads of America Council services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Crossroads of America Council to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.Crossroads of America Council websites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Crossroads of America Council or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Crossroads of America Council; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Crossroads of America Council, or the public.Use of CookiesThe Crossroads of America Council website use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Crossroads of America Council pages, or register with Crossroads of America Council site or services, a cookie helps Crossroads of America Council to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Crossroads of America Council Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Crossroads of America Council features that you customized.You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Crossroads of America Council services or websites you visit.Security of Personal InformationCrossroads of America Council secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Crossroads of America Council secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.Changes to this StatementCrossroads of America Council will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Crossroads of America Council encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Crossroads of America Council is protecting your information.Contact InformationCrossroads of America Council welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Crossroads of America Council has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Crossroads of America Council at admin@crossroadsbsa.org. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
Golden-Burke Scout Center7125 Fall Creek Road NorthIndianapolis, IN 46256Phone: (317) 813-7125Toll Free: (877) 925-1900Fax: (317) 813-7126
© 2020 Crossroads of America Council, BSA – All Rights Reserved
